A Guide to the Walther F. Goebel papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA162
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Laboratory Notebooks
  - Laboratory Notebook - Goebel, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory Notebook, "The Derivatives of Citraconic Acid", Munich, 1923-1924 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Goebel, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory Notebook, "Carbohydrate Synthesizing Enzymes", 1941 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Goebel, 1969-1970; 1 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Goebel, 1969-1970; 2 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Goebel, 1970-1971; 1 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Goebel, 1970-1971; 2 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Goebel, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Goebel, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Laboratory Technician lab notebooks
  - Laboratory Notebook - Miller, 1947-1949; 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Miller, 1947-1949; 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Megatherium Book 1, Laboratory Notebook - Miller, 1951-1954; 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Megatherium Book 1, Laboratory Notebook - Miller, 1951-1954; 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Miller, 1952-1954 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Colicine K, Book I, Laboratory Notebook - Miller, 1953-1956; 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Colicine K, Book I, Laboratory Notebook - Miller, 1953-1956; 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Colicine K, Book II, Laboratory Notebook - Miller, 1955-1956; 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Colicine K, Book II, Laboratory Notebook - Miller, 1955-1956; 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Sapelli, 1957-1959 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Sapelli, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Sapelli, 1961-1963; 1 of 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Sapelli, 1961-1963; 2 of 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Sapelli Work on: E. Coli K 12. Fractionation of Horse & Rabbit Sera, Neutralization Tests on Above Sera, 1963-1965 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Sapelli Chom & Sephodex Filtration of Col K Protein Growth of L & T in Presence of Mitomyein, Also Phenol Dissociation, 1964-1966 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Sapelli, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Irwin Rude (Researcher in Goebel Lab), 1960-1961; 1 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Irwin Rude (Researcher in Goebel Lab), 1960-1961; 2 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Schleich, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Raphael, Marie-Ann, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Iliana Barson, 1971-1973; 1 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Iliana Barson, 1971-1973; 2 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Graduate & Undergraduate Course Notebooks, 1960-1973
  - Laboratory Notebook - Goebel, "Chemistry 104D" Undergrad. University of Illinois, Urbana, 1916-1920 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory Notebook - Goebel, Manual for "The Elements of Qualitative Analysis" Undergrad. University of Illinois, Urbana, 1917 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Goebel Course Notebook "Chemistry 14a" Undergrad. University of Illinois, Urbana, 1918 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Goebel Course Notebook "Chemistry 14a" Undergrad. University of Illinois, Urbana, 1918 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Goebel Course Notebook "Chemistry 104a" Graduate University of Illinois, Urbana, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Goebel Course Notebook "Chemistry 14c" Graduate University of Illinois, Urbana, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Goebel Course Notebook "Chemistry 14d" Graduate University, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Goebel Course Notebook "Course Identification missing" Graduate, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Graduate Course Notebooks, Seminars, Reports, 1921-1976
  - Goebel Course Notebook "Physiological Chemistry" (Doodles P 234) Graduate University of Illinois, Urbana, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Goebel Course Notebook on "Bacterial Viruses" (Bacteriophage CSH), Cold Spring Harbor, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports - Working Draft, 1934-1951 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - ACS (New York Section) Meeting, N.Y.C., 1936 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Memorial Hospital Opening of Sloane-Kettering Institute of Cancer Research, Invitation & Program, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - International Phage Symposium Abbaye Royaumont, France, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Science Meetings April 27-30, Washington D.C. November 16-18 Bloomington, Indiana, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Progress Report "The Chemical & Immunological Nature of Colocines", 1964 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Seminar, Mosbach, Germany, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - 1966 Goebel RU Review - Rufus Cole 1972-1966, 1966-1972 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Gesellschaft für Immunologie e.v., 1970 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Annual Reports - Working Draft, 1952-1976 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Reprints - Goebel
  - Reprints - Goebel, 1922-1929 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Reprints - Goebel, 1930-1933 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Reprints - Goebel, 1934-1935 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Reprints - Goebel, 1937-1939 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Reprints - Goebel, 1940-1947 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Reprints - Goebel, 1948-1949 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Reprints - Goebel, 1950-1958 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Reprints - Goebel, RU Quarterly, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Reprints - Goebel, Book Review, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Reprints - Goebel [Includes 5 not listed in Goebel Bibliography], 1960-1964 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Reprints - Goebel [Includes 5 not listed in Goebel Bibliography], 1965-1975 (Box 23, Folder 6)